https://codibug.com/codi-frazier/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy - CodiBug.com
Skip to content (Press Enter)
Photos
A Wedding!
Around the House
Birthday 7/01/02
Birthday Party!
Shriner’s Hospital
Slumber Party!
Photos
A Wedding!
Around the House
Birthday 7/01/02
Birthday Party!
Shriner’s Hospital
Slumber Party!
Privacy Policy
Welcome to https://codibug.com (the “Site”).We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to make use of the various services offered by CodiBug.com (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).
“Personally Identifiable Information”
Refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.
What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?
We may collect basic user browser data from all of our Visitors. We also collect, but do not distribute, the information provided by the visitor when using any of our interactive services such as the guestbook.
What organizations are collecting the information?
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third-party service vendors (such as the guestbook service) who may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors.
How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.
With whom may the information may be shared?
Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may be shared with other Authorized
Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with other Authorized Customers.
We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our
Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors.
We also offer the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by
us or by any agency acting on our behalf.
How is Personally
Identifiable Information stored?
Personally Identifiable Information collected by
CodiBug.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of
CodiBug.com except for use as indicated above.
What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.
Are Cookies Used on the Site?
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using https://codibug.com, with the drawback that certain features of website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Cookies used by our service providers
Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website. You can find more details about which cookies are used in our cookies info page.
How does CodiBug.com use login information?
CodiBug.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.
What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?
CodiBug.com has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors. Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know the basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility. Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information. Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with the law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.
How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?
The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information.  While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering, and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.
Your rights
These are summarized rights that you have under data protection law
The right to access
The right to rectification
The right to erasure
The right to restrict processing
The right to object to processing
The right to data portability
The right to complain to a supervisory authority
The right to withdraw consent
What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.
Links:
https://codibug.com contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
Please Sign My GuestbookSONGS FOR CODICodi Bug by Michael Mugrage
https://www.codibug.com/codis_song.wavWe Love Codi by Carol Adamshttps://www.codibug.com/we_love_codi.wavThrough the Eyes of a Child by Jennifer KravassiSite Navigation
Codi Frazier
Guestbook
Contact
My Story
Artwork
Codi’s Life
Important Links
Parents
CodiBug.com.
Preschool and Kindergarten | Developed By
Rara Theme.
